<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipes on Cup O Tea</title>
    <link>http://example.org/recipes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recipes on Cup O Tea</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 22:41:57 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bo Lo Bao (Pineapple Bun)</title>
      <link>http://example.org/recipes/bo_lo_bao/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 14:11:59 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/recipes/bo_lo_bao/</guid>
      <description>Notes  Contrary to popular belief, pineapples buns don&amp;rsquo;t actually contain any pineapple ingredients. It only refers to the shape of the bun and topping.  Topping  Combine melted butter(4 tablespoons), milk(2 teaspoons),1 egg, 1/2 teaspoons vanilla extract, and 2/3 cups sugar Stir until even smooth texture Add the dry ingredients: 1/2 cup sugar, 1 cup flour, 1/2 teaspoon baking powder, 1/2 teaspoon baking soda, pinch of salt Stir into all combined Press into dough log Wrap the dough with plastic wrap, then roll into cylinder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japanese Milkbread</title>
      <link>http://example.org/recipes/japanese_milkbread/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 08:25:34 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/recipes/japanese_milkbread/</guid>
      <description>Notes  tangzhong is responsible for the light, fluffy texture in Asian bakery  good base for sandwiches and toasts    Tangzhong  a roux with flour and water warming to activate the gluten in the flour before even mixing with other ingredients  Instructions  Make some tangzhong slightly ahead Put 2 tablespoons of bread flour and 6 tablespoons of water in small pan. Mix until smooth and no lumps remain-before turning on the heat Warm the flour gently over medium-low heat until it thickens, stirring constantly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Bagels</title>
      <link>http://example.org/recipes/bagels/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 09:58:29 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/recipes/bagels/</guid>
      <description>Directions Bagels  Bloom your yeast first. Get 297 grams of water at about 100 degrees F and add 10 grams of yeast (~ 1 tablespoon) and 23 grams of sugar (~1.5 tablespoon). Give a stir to immerse yeast in water. Let it rest for 10 minutes. The yeast will puff up. Stir again. Add 500g (~3.5 cups) bread flour, 6g salt (~1.5 teaspoons)and the yeast to a bowl. Turn dough out onto work surface(or in the bowl, if large enough) and knead the dough for ~10 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
